[{"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "a.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "b.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "c.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "d.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "e.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "f.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "g.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "h.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "i.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "j.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "k.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "l.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "m.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["afilias-nst.info.", "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "c0.info.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["afilias-nst.info.", "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "b2.info.afilias-nst.org."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["afilias-nst.info.", "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "a0.info.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["afilias-nst.info.", "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "b0.info.afilias-nst.org."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["afilias-nst.info.", "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "d0.info.afilias-nst.org."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["org.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["org.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["org.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["org.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["org.afilias-nst.info.", "."], "server": "c0.org.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["org.afilias-nst.info.", "."], "server": "d0.org.afilias-nst.org."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["org.afilias-nst.info.", "."], "server": "a0.org.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "a.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "b.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "c.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "d.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "e.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "f.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "g.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "h.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "i.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "j.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "k.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "l.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "m.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.afilias-nst.info.", "."], "server": "a0.info.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.afilias-nst.info.", "."], "server": "b0.info.afilias-nst.org."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.afilias-nst.info.", "."], "server": "c0.info.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.afilias-nst.info.", "."], "server": "d0.info.afilias-nst.org."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "a.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "b.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "c.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "d.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "e.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "f.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "g.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "h.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "i.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "j.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "k.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "l.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "m.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.afilias-nst.info.", "."], "server": "a0.info.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.afilias-nst.info.", "."], "server": "b0.info.afilias-nst.org."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.afilias-nst.info.", "."], "server": "c0.info.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.afilias-nst.info.", "."], "server": "d0.info.afilias-nst.org."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "a.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "b.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "c.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "d.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "e.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "f.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "g.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "h.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "i.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "j.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "k.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "l.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "m.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["afilias-nst.org.", "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "c0.org.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["afilias-nst.org.", "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "a0.org.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["afilias-nst.org.", "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "b2.org.afilias-nst.org."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["afilias-nst.org.", "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "a2.org.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["afilias-nst.org.", "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "d0.org.afilias-nst.org."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["info.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["info.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["info.afilias-nst.org.", "."], "server": "d0.info.afilias-nst.org."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["info.afilias-nst.org.", "."], "server": "b0.info.afilias-nst.org."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["info.afilias-nst.org.", "."], "server": "c0.info.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["info.afilias-nst.org.", "."], "server": "a0.info.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "a.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "b.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "c.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "d.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "e.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "f.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "g.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "h.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "i.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "j.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "k.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "l.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "m.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.afilias-nst.info.", "."], "server": "d0.info.afilias-nst.org."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.afilias-nst.info.", "."], "server": "a0.info.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.afilias-nst.info.", "."], "server": "a2.info.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.afilias-nst.info.", "."], "server": "b2.info.afilias-nst.org."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.afilias-nst.info.", "."], "server": "b0.info.afilias-nst.org."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.afilias-nst.info.", "."], "server": "c0.info.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "a.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "b.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "c.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "d.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "e.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "f.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "g.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "h.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "i.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "j.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "k.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "l.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "m.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["afilias-nst.org.", "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "c0.org.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["afilias-nst.org.", "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "a2.org.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["afilias-nst.org.", "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "a0.org.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["afilias-nst.org.", "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "d0.org.afilias-nst.org."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["afilias-nst.org.", "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "b2.org.afilias-nst.org."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["info.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["info.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["info.afilias-nst.org.", "."], "server": "a0.info.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["info.afilias-nst.org.", "."], "server": "b0.info.afilias-nst.org."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["info.afilias-nst.org.", "."], "server": "d0.info.afilias-nst.org."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["info.afilias-nst.org.", "."], "server": "c0.info.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "a.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "b.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "c.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "d.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "e.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "f.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "g.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "h.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "i.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "j.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "k.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "l.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "m.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["afilias-nst.org.", "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "c0.org.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["afilias-nst.org.", "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "d0.org.afilias-nst.org."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["afilias-nst.org.", "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "a2.org.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["afilias-nst.org.", "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "b2.org.afilias-nst.org."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["afilias-nst.org.", "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "a0.org.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["info.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["info.afilias-nst.org.", "."], "server": "a0.info.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["info.afilias-nst.org.", "."], "server": "b0.info.afilias-nst.org."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["info.afilias-nst.org.", "."], "server": "c0.info.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["info.afilias-nst.org.", "."], "server": "d0.info.afilias-nst.org."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "a.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "b.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "c.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "d.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "e.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "f.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "g.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "h.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "i.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "j.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "k.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "l.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "m.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["afilias-nst.info.", "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "b0.info.afilias-nst.org."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["afilias-nst.info.", "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "a0.info.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["afilias-nst.info.", "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "d0.info.afilias-nst.org."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["afilias-nst.info.", "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "c0.info.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["dig.afilias-nst.info.", "."], "server": "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["dig.afilias-nst.info.", "."], "server": "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["dig.afilias-nst.info.", "."], "server": "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["dig.afilias-nst.info.", "."], "server": "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "a.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "b.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "c.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "d.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "e.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "f.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "g.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "h.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "i.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "j.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "k.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "l.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "m.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["afilias-nst.info.", "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "b0.info.afilias-nst.org."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["afilias-nst.info.", "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "d0.info.afilias-nst.org."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["afilias-nst.info.", "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "a0.info.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["afilias-nst.info.", "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "c0.info.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["dig.afilias-nst.info.", "."], "server": "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["dig.afilias-nst.info.", "."], "server": "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["dig.afilias-nst.info.", "."], "server": "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["dig.afilias-nst.info.", "."], "server": "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "a.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "b.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "c.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "d.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "e.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "f.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "g.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "h.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "i.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "j.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "k.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "l.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "m.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["afilias-nst.info.", "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "a0.info.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["afilias-nst.info.", "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "c0.info.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["afilias-nst.info.", "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "b0.info.afilias-nst.org."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["afilias-nst.info.", "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "d0.info.afilias-nst.org."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["dig.afilias-nst.info.", "."], "server": "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["dig.afilias-nst.info.", "."], "server": "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["dig.afilias-nst.info.", "."], "server": "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["dig.afilias-nst.info.", "."], "server": "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "a.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "b.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "c.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "d.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "e.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "f.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "g.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "h.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "i.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "j.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "k.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "l.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "m.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["afilias-nst.info.", "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "d0.info.afilias-nst.org."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["afilias-nst.info.", "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "c0.info.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["afilias-nst.info.", "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "a0.info.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["afilias-nst.info.", "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "b0.info.afilias-nst.org."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["dig.afilias-nst.info.", "."], "server": "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["dig.afilias-nst.info.", "."], "server": "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["dig.afilias-nst.info.", "."], "server": "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["dig.afilias-nst.info.", "."], "server": "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "a.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "b.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "c.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "d.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "e.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "f.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "g.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "h.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "i.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "j.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "k.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "l.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "m.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.afilias-nst.org.", "."], "server": "b2.org.afilias-nst.org."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.afilias-nst.org.", "."], "server": "c0.org.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.afilias-nst.org.", "."], "server": "a0.org.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.afilias-nst.org.", "."], "server": "d0.org.afilias-nst.org."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.afilias-nst.org.", "."], "server": "a2.org.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.afilias-nst.org.", "."], "server": "b0.org.afilias-nst.org."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "a.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "b.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "c.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "d.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "e.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "f.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "g.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "h.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "i.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "j.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "k.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "l.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "m.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["afilias-nst.info.", "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "a0.info.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["afilias-nst.info.", "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "d0.info.afilias-nst.org."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["afilias-nst.info.", "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "b0.info.afilias-nst.org."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["afilias-nst.info.", "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "c0.info.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["org.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["org.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["org.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["org.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["org.afilias-nst.info.", "."], "server": "c0.org.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["org.afilias-nst.info.", "."], "server": "d0.org.afilias-nst.org."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["org.afilias-nst.info.", "."], "server": "a0.org.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "a.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "b.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "c.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "d.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "e.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "f.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "g.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "h.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "i.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "j.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "k.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "l.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "m.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.afilias-nst.org.", "."], "server": "d0.org.afilias-nst.org."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.afilias-nst.org.", "."], "server": "a0.org.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.afilias-nst.org.", "."], "server": "b0.org.afilias-nst.org."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.afilias-nst.org.", "."], "server": "c0.org.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.afilias-nst.org.", "."], "server": "b2.org.afilias-nst.org."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.afilias-nst.org.", "."], "server": "a2.org.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "a.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "b.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "c.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "d.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "e.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "f.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "g.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "h.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "i.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "j.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "k.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "l.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["info.", "c0.info.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.info.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.info.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.info.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "m.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["afilias-nst.info.", "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "a0.info.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["afilias-nst.info.", "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "c0.info.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["afilias-nst.info.", "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "b2.info.afilias-nst.org."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["afilias-nst.info.", "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "d0.info.afilias-nst.org."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["afilias-nst.info.", "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "a2.info.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["afilias-nst.info.", "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "b0.info.afilias-nst.org."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["org.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "a0.dig.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["org.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "b0.dig.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["org.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "c0.dig.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["org.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "d0.dig.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["org.afilias-nst.info.", "."], "server": "a0.org.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["org.afilias-nst.info.", "."], "server": "b0.org.afilias-nst.org."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["org.afilias-nst.info.", "."], "server": "c0.org.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "authority": ["org.afilias-nst.info.", "."], "server": "d0.org.afilias-nst.org."}, {"answer": ["d.root-servers.net.", "g.root-servers.net.", "h.root-servers.net.", "c.root-servers.net.", "m.root-servers.net.", "b.root-servers.net.", "i.root-servers.net.", "j.root-servers.net.", "e.root-servers.net.", "l.root-servers.net.", "f.root-servers.net.", "k.root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "flags": 33792, "question": ".", "authority": [], "server": "a.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": ["d.root-servers.net.", "b.root-servers.net.", "i.root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net.", "k.root-servers.net.", "l.root-servers.net.", "h.root-servers.net.", "g.root-servers.net.", "c.root-servers.net.", "j.root-servers.net.", "e.root-servers.net.", "m.root-servers.net.", "f.root-servers.net."], "flags": 33792, "question": ".", "authority": [], "server": "b.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": ["k.root-servers.net.", "b.root-servers.net.", "j.root-servers.net.", "c.root-servers.net.", "f.root-servers.net.", "i.root-servers.net.", "h.root-servers.net.", "g.root-servers.net.", "d.root-servers.net.", "e.root-servers.net.", "m.root-servers.net.", "l.root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "flags": 33792, "question": ".", "authority": [], "server": "c.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": ["e.root-servers.net.", "i.root-servers.net.", "d.root-servers.net.", "k.root-servers.net.", "l.root-servers.net.", "h.root-servers.net.", "c.root-servers.net.", "j.root-servers.net.", "f.root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net.", "b.root-servers.net.", "m.root-servers.net.", "g.root-servers.net."], "flags": 33792, "question": ".", "authority": [], "server": "d.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": ["f.root-servers.net.", "k.root-servers.net.", "l.root-servers.net.", "d.root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net.", "b.root-servers.net.", "e.root-servers.net.", "m.root-servers.net.", "c.root-servers.net.", "i.root-servers.net.", "h.root-servers.net.", "j.root-servers.net.", "g.root-servers.net."], "flags": 33792, "question": ".", "authority": [], "server": "e.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": ["l.root-servers.net.", "f.root-servers.net.", "d.root-servers.net.", "j.root-servers.net.", "h.root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net.", "i.root-servers.net.", "k.root-servers.net.", "m.root-servers.net.", "e.root-servers.net.", "g.root-servers.net.", "b.root-servers.net.", "c.root-servers.net."], "flags": 33792, "question": ".", "authority": [], "server": "f.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": ["d.root-servers.net.", "g.root-servers.net.", "j.root-servers.net.", "i.root-servers.net.", "e.root-servers.net.", "m.root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net.", "f.root-servers.net.", "b.root-servers.net.", "k.root-servers.net.", "h.root-servers.net.", "l.root-servers.net.", "c.root-servers.net."], "flags": 33792, "question": ".", "authority": [], "server": "g.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": ["a.root-servers.net.", "b.root-servers.net.", "c.root-servers.net.", "d.root-servers.net.", "e.root-servers.net.", "f.root-servers.net.", "g.root-servers.net.", "h.root-servers.net.", "i.root-servers.net.", "j.root-servers.net.", "k.root-servers.net.", "l.root-servers.net.", "m.root-servers.net."], "flags": 33792, "question": ".", "authority": [], "server": "h.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": ["k.root-servers.net.", "h.root-servers.net.", "g.root-servers.net.", "d.root-servers.net.", "c.root-servers.net.", "l.root-servers.net.", "b.root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net.", "i.root-servers.net.", "m.root-servers.net.", "j.root-servers.net.", "e.root-servers.net.", "f.root-servers.net."], "flags": 33792, "question": ".", "authority": [], "server": "i.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": ["a.root-servers.net.", "d.root-servers.net.", "j.root-servers.net.", "e.root-servers.net.", "f.root-servers.net.", "b.root-servers.net.", "c.root-servers.net.", "g.root-servers.net.", "k.root-servers.net.", "i.root-servers.net.", "l.root-servers.net.", "h.root-servers.net.", "m.root-servers.net."], "flags": 33792, "question": ".", "authority": [], "server": "j.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": ["i.root-servers.net.", "h.root-servers.net.", "m.root-servers.net.", "j.root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net.", "e.root-servers.net.", "d.root-servers.net.", "l.root-servers.net.", "c.root-servers.net.", "k.root-servers.net.", "g.root-servers.net.", "b.root-servers.net.", "f.root-servers.net."], "flags": 33792, "question": ".", "authority": [], "server": "k.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": ["m.root-servers.net.", "d.root-servers.net.", "f.root-servers.net.", "j.root-servers.net.", "i.root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net.", "b.root-servers.net.", "h.root-servers.net.", "e.root-servers.net.", "l.root-servers.net.", "c.root-servers.net.", "g.root-servers.net.", "k.root-servers.net."], "flags": 33792, "question": ".", "authority": [], "server": "l.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": ["h.root-servers.net.", "k.root-servers.net.", "d.root-servers.net.", "b.root-servers.net.", "g.root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net.", "c.root-servers.net.", "l.root-servers.net.", "f.root-servers.net.", "j.root-servers.net.", "e.root-servers.net.", "m.root-servers.net.", "i.root-servers.net."], "flags": 33792, "question": ".", "authority": [], "server": "m.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "a.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "b.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "c.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "d.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "e.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "f.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "g.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "h.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "i.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "j.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "k.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info."], "server": "l.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.", "a0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "c0.org.afilias-nst.info.", "a2.org.afilias-nst.info.", "d0.org.afilias-nst.org.", "b0.org.afilias-nst.org."], "server": "m.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.afilias-nst.org.", "."], "server": "a0.org.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.afilias-nst.org.", "."], "server": "b2.org.afilias-nst.org."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.afilias-nst.org.", "."], "server": "a2.org.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.afilias-nst.org.", "."], "server": "c0.org.afilias-nst.info."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.afilias-nst.org.", "."], "server": "b0.org.afilias-nst.org."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "b2.org.afilias-nst.org.", "authority": ["org.afilias-nst.org.", "."], "server": "d0.org.afilias-nst.org."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "d.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "a.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "d.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "b.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "d.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "c.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "d.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "d.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "d.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "e.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "d.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "f.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "d.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "g.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "d.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "h.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "d.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "i.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "d.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "j.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "d.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "k.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "d.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "l.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "d.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "m.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "g.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "a.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "g.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "b.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "g.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "c.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "g.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "d.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "g.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "e.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "g.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "f.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "g.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "g.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "g.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "h.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "g.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "i.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "g.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "j.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "g.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "k.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "g.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "l.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "g.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "m.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "h.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "a.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "h.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "b.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "h.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "c.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "h.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "d.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "h.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "e.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "h.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "f.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "h.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "g.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "h.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "h.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "h.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "i.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "h.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "j.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "h.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "k.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "h.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "l.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "h.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "m.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "c.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "a.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "c.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "b.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "c.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "c.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "c.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "d.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "c.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "e.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "c.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "f.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "c.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "g.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "c.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "h.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "c.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "i.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "c.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "j.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "c.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "k.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "c.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "l.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "c.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "m.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "m.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "a.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "m.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "b.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "m.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "c.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "m.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "d.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "m.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "e.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "m.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "f.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "m.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "g.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "m.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "h.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "m.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "i.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "m.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "j.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "m.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "k.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "m.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "l.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "m.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "m.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "b.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "a.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "b.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "b.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "b.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "c.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "b.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "d.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "b.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "e.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "b.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "f.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "b.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "g.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "b.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "h.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "b.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "i.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "b.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "j.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "b.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "k.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "b.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "l.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "b.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "m.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "i.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "a.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "i.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "b.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "i.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "c.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "i.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "d.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "i.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "e.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "i.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "f.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "i.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "g.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "i.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "h.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "i.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "i.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "i.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "j.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "i.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "k.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "i.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "l.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "i.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "m.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "j.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "a.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "j.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "b.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "j.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "c.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "j.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "d.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "j.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "e.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "j.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "f.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "j.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "g.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "j.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "h.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "j.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "i.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "j.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "j.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "j.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "k.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "j.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "l.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "j.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "m.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "e.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "a.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "e.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "b.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "e.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "c.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "e.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "d.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "e.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "e.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "e.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "f.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "e.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "g.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "e.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "h.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "e.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "i.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "e.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "j.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "e.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "k.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "e.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "l.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "e.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "m.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "l.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "a.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "l.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "b.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "l.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "c.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "l.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "d.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "l.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "e.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "l.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "f.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "l.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "g.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "l.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "h.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "l.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "i.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "l.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "j.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "l.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "k.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "l.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "l.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "l.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "m.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "f.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "a.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "f.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "b.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "f.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "c.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "f.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "d.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "f.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "e.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "f.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "f.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "f.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "g.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "f.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "h.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "f.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "i.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "f.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "j.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "f.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "k.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "f.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "l.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "f.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "m.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "k.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "b.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "k.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "c.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "k.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "d.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "k.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "e.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "k.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "f.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "k.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "g.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "k.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "h.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "k.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "i.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "k.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "j.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "k.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "k.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "k.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "l.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "k.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "m.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "a.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "a.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "a.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "b.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "a.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "c.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "a.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "d.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "a.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "e.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "a.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "f.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "a.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "g.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "a.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "h.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "a.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "i.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "a.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "j.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "a.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "k.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "a.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "l.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "a.root-servers.net.", "authority": ["root-servers.net.", "a.root-servers.net."], "server": "m.root-servers.net."}]